http://www.tourking.us/store/index.php?main_page=privacy

About Us
Welcome to our Store!
Welcome to Tour King. We have been offering quality accessories for motorcycle riders since 2001, when we opened for business as RideCool.com. In 2013 we acquired the Tour King brand from its founder. At that time, Tour King was almost 20 years old and had established itself as a favorite with riders across the country.
The Tour King cover is known for its great design, quality construction, and durability. Over the years, other products have been introduced with the same desire for quality and durability. All Tour King branded items continue to be made in Texas with quality US made components.
Customer service is of the utmost importance to us so please share with us any questions or concerns about our products. And share your satisfaction with your friends.
Customer Service
Shipping
Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Etiam interdum feugiat ipsum vehicula sollicitudin. Integer sed lacus eget risus consectetur ullamcorper. Pellentesque rutrum ullamcorper faucibus. Nam porttitor iaculis enim, mattis tristique velit tristique bibendum.
Shop with Confidence
Here you can write a few short sentencs about why your customers can buy with conficence from your store.
You might also want to outline your payment options here.
Information
Customer Service
About Us
Log In
Create Account
Shipping & Returns
Privacy Notice
Conditions of Use
Categories
Tour King Half-Covers70Bargain Center4Hanging Helmet Bag1Tour King Gold Wing Dash Mats1Tour King Cup Holders5Gold Wing GL1800 Remote Cover1Butler Extreme Mug Systems4Cooling Bandanas3Specials ...
Home
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
SECTION 1 - WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?
When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address.
When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.
Email marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products and other updates.
SECTION 2 - CONSENT
How do you get my consent?
When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.
If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.
How do I withdraw my consent?
If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at shop@tourking.us or mailing us at: Tour King 3400 An County Rd 370, Palestine, TX, 75801, United States
SECTION 3 - DISCLOSURE
We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.
Payment:
All payments to Tour King are completed offsite by third party services. Tour King does not process or store any cardholders information on site. Some third party services may allow you to save your payment information for future purchases. Please review their individual privacy policies
All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.
PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.
SECTION 5 - THIRD-PARTY SERVICES
In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.
However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.
For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.
In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located in a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.
As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.
Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.
Links
When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.
SECTION 6 - SECURITY
To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.
If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption.
Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.
COOKIES
Here is a list of cookies that we use. We’ve listed them here so you can choose if you want to opt-out of cookies or not.
_session_id, unique token, sessional, Allows Shopify to store information about your session (referrer, landing page, etc).
cart, unique token, persistent for 2 weeks, Stores information about the contents of your cart.
storefront_digest, unique token, indefinite If the shop has a password, this is used to determine if the current visitor has access.
SECTION 7 - AGE OF CONSENT
By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.
SECTION 8 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.
If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.
QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION
If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at shop@tourking.us or by mail at Tour King, 3400 An County Rd 370, Palestine, TX, 75801, United States
Back
Specials  [more]
Your IP Address is:
72.182.10.230
